A Guide to the Papers of the Twin Oaks Community 1955(1974-1983)
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Twin Oaks Community 1955(1974-1983)
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
9840-r
This collection consists of ca. 900 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access is restricted to those having the written permission of the Community's Board of Planners.
Acquisition Information
This collection was loaned to the University of Virginia Library on December 21, 1995, by the Archives of the Twin Oaks Community's Board of Planners.
Scope and Content Information
Papers of the Twin Oaks Community pertain to economic planning and the planning commission of the community. Financial reports, questionnaires/worksheets, surveys, charts, drawings, reference material and printed ephemera are included.
Some of the reference material pertains to the Ananda Community in Nevada City, Calif.
Contents List
- Economic Planning 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Economic Planning: 1981 Plan 1981 (Box 1)
- Economic Planning: 1982 Plan 1982, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Economic Planning: 1983 Plan 1983, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Economic Planning: Planners Reports 1982-1983 (Box 2)
- Economic Planning: Planwritting Questionnaires/Worksheets 1982 (Box 2)
- Economic Planning: Planwriting Questionnaires/Worksheets 1983 (Box 2)
- Economic Planning: Priority Requests 1982 (Box 2)
- Economic Planning: Priority Requests 1983 (Box 2)
- Economic Planning: Trade-Off Areas 1981-1982 (Box 2)
- Planning Commission: Reference-Notes 1974-1977 (Box 3)
  includes the list of new categories for these files
- Planning Commission: Reference--Archives 1969-1974, n.d. (Box 3)
- Planning Commission--Reference 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  re Planning, General Reference; Board of Supervisor Notes
- Planning Commission: Reference 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  re Agriculture; Development Plans; Land Purchase Info
- Planning Commission: Reference 1955-1975 (Box 3)
  re Watershed Info; Zoning; Survey Samples I; Greene County Master Plan
- Planning Commission: Ananda Master Plan 1974-1975 (Box 3)
- Planning Commission: Survey 1975-1977; n.d. (Box 1)
  re Children; Cognitive Maps; Cultural Values Tab; Population Models
- Planning Commission: Survey--Cultural Values Data [1975] (Box 3)
- Planning Commission: Survey--Functional Relationships Three [1975] (Box 3)